friv.rest 2017-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Friv Games - Juegos Friv , Jogos Friv , Jeux de Friv

**Privacy Policy for friv.rest**

At friv.rest, the privacy of our visitors is taken very seriously. This document outlines the types of personal information that are received and collected by friv.rest and how we do use it.

**Concerning Log Files**  
Friv.rest makes use of log files, a common practice between other websites. All the information contained in the log files include internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks for analytics, management moviment tracking and gathering of demographic information purposes. IP addresses and likewise are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Friv.rest stores information about its users preferences, recording information about the very same user regarding the pages accessed or visited and concerning browser type so that the navigation is customized to it.

**About DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve its ads on friv.rest.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to friv.rest and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology that sends advertisements and links directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address. Other technologies (like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see, so that it will fit the users’ preferences.

The website friv.rest has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of each one of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out from what our privacy policy doesn’t apply to.

To disable cookies, do it through your individual browser options or settings. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ official websites.

**Links**

All the websites to which we hyperlink are responsible for their own privacy policy. Be aware of them and make sure to read all the lines of their privacy policy to know their specific conditions. This privacy statement applies solely to this website.
